[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Anyway , after much yelling and cussing I hung up , grabbed a cab , and went to Geno 's .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grabbed\", does the participant \"cab\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" Success comes before work \" only in the dictionary\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comes\", does the participant \"Success\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Sheriff 's deputies in Louisiana made a third arrest Wednesday in the ongoing investigation of a case involving allegations of sexual abuse of children and animals at a Ponchatoula , La. , church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"arrest\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Miramar was founded September 20 1888 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"founded\", does the participant \"Miramar\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" I 'm pretty suspicious of making broad generalizations , \" however , he cautioned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cautioned\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is NO such thing as a BTA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Because of the ants I dropped them to a 3 star .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I loved my stay here and if ever back in the area , I will be staying here again .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loved\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Sunni AMS told Iraqis , \" You sinned when you participated with occupation forces in the assault on Najaf , and beware lest you repeat this same sin in Fallujah .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"AMS\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"On August 21st , 2009 I ordered furniture from Hickory Furniture Mart and contracted for HDS to deliver it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deliver\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Any of the tip - top places have great ice - cream , get them to mix it up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cream\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"colorado beat texas a&m .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"beat\", does the participant \"colorado\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It put hair on my chest and thanks to the owner s advice I invested vanguard , got myself a woman like Jerry , and became a republican .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invested\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had to throw out about 80 percent of our meals because the food tasted so horrible .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"throw\", does the participant \"percent\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"His press release following the hearing renewed the call for \" refunds . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renewed\", does the participant \"call\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Leads who are responsible for Associates are as follows :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"Leads\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"analyzed\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"To the north in Lebanon , there is serious debate within Hezbollah about entering the Lebanese political process in light of Syria 's promised withdrawal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"entering\", does the participant \"process\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She had her cards memorized as well as everyone else s ( when you play you 'll see why you can know everyone else s hands ! ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Communists agreed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"agreed\", does the participant \"Communists\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no complaints about the service I received .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"complaints\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"On August 21st , 2009 I ordered furniture from Hickory Furniture Mart and contracted for HDS to deliver it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deliver\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They offer a good portions at a great price , it 's enough food to fill you up , but you do n't ever feel like you ate too much .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The family 's attorney advises me that Aafia had no knowledge of chemicals ( and that would not appear to be her training ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"advises\", does the participant \"attorney\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Their chauvinisms got to the point that even they themselves hated each other .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hated\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I took the receipt and the metal that did not fit and asked Pomper for my money back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I decided that Nicki would just have to wait on her own .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"decided\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"rights\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Is there any other way to communicate or do your friends only understand text .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"friends\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dismissed\", does the participant \"government\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The latter usually consider human beings a threat but the polar bear considers humans a snack , experts said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"consider\", does the participant \"beings\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"To the north in Lebanon , there is serious debate within Hezbollah about entering the Lebanese political process in light of Syria 's promised withdrawal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"entering\", does the participant \"process\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"share\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"None of them did , and most importantly , the winning bidders did not .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"None\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"roof\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"vet\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We love Little Farmer\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"Farmer\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Midas has the most high tech equipment in town & I guarantee you if they told you it was electrical then in deed it s electrical !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Midas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"James J. Hoecker , the former Federal Energy Regulatory Commission chairman , defended making the December decision and also defended Winter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defended\", does the participant \"Hoecker\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I thought to get a decent pizza the only way was at a fancy restaurant , and I have to get a whole pie .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( Participants pledged to raise at least $ 100,000 by bundling together cheques of up to $ 1,000 from friends and family .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pledged\", does the participant \"Participants\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The lady at pet smart said 4 hours , but on places on the net it says 10 to 12 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"lady\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"Sharon\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"hey kido u made me smile\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"kido\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My wife has a slight impediment in her speech .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"impediment\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But he suffers the severe effects of the aftermath , and we are all suffering along with him now , since he is the most powerful man in the world .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suffers\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached is a forecast for the rest of the summer for the X ( NWP and PGT ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"forecast\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"As with so much climate research , not everyone agrees with these dire predictions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"agrees\", does the participant \"everyone\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bush asked for permission to go to Alabama to work on a Senate campaign .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As a result there was a problem with the weapon jamming .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"problem\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defied\", does the participant \"Winter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"that\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"India 's Andaman and Nicobar Islands comprise more than 500 islands lying 1,000 kilometers east of Sri Lanka in the Bay of Bengal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comprise\", does the participant \"Islands\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ended up paying much more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paying\", does the participant \"more\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interfere\", does the participant \"State\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"George Harrison said that he is tired of listening to people talk about John Lennon ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"talk\", does the participant \"people\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She gave me amazing pictures at an amazing price and made my wedding day so memorable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"She\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" I 'm pretty suspicious of making broad generalizations , \" however , he cautioned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cautioned\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A coalition forces spokesman confirmed they had not received \" any weapons from Bosnia \" and added they were \" not aware of any purchases for Iraq from Bosnia \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"confirmed\", does the participant \"spokesman\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"ALITO filed a dissenting opinion , in which SCALIA and THOMAS joined as to Parts I through III .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"ALITO\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We were booked at the Sheraton with a number of other out - of - town wedding guests .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We accecpt : Visa , MasterCard , Amex , Dinner s Club / Carte Blanche , & Personal Checks / Money Orders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accecpt\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is a forecast for the rest of the summer for the X ( NWP and PGT ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"forecast\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Terrell , a CIA asset originally recruited for the Contra effort , identifies the man attempting to recruit him into the Philippine scheme as Oliver North ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"identifies\", does the participant \"Terrell\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I sent a customer of mine to you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In my first week , I made about $ 25.00 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Lopez addressed the note which I had written , sealed it with his sleeve - link , and sent it by the hand of the servant , Jose .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"addressed\", does the participant \"Lopez\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Archibald says that in a campaign full of dedicated workers , Mr. Bush was not one of them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Archibald\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I took the cage and place it next to the couch .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My car broke down and roadside towed my vehicle to Sussman Kia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"towed\", does the participant \"roadside\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Denial of the status of marriage to those who would freely accept its responsibilities creates legal and economic inequities and social injustice .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"creates\", does the participant \"inequities\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In the meantime , we extend our best wishes for a safe and happy holiday season .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"$\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The millions who died in the Iran - Iraq war had nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"millions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the participant \"Allawi\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We felt that the main shows on the Mariner of the Seas were better .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"felt\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A coalition forces spokesman confirmed they had not received \" any weapons from Bosnia \" and added they were \" not aware of any purchases for Iraq from Bosnia \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"confirmed\", does the participant \"spokesman\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I spoke with Mike Collins [ 203-719-8385 ( phone ) and 203-719-7031 ( fax ) ] who conrfirmed to me that the cap included the remaining 2.5 + million remaining shares .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The BBC 's Alastair Leithead in New Orleans says there is panic as vital supplies run out .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Leithead\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Midas has the most high tech equipment in town & I guarantee you if they told you it was electrical then in deed it s electrical !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Midas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I wish all happy holidays , and moreso , peace on earth .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"holidays\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" They can freely write anything they like about our prophet , but if one raises doubts about the Holocaust he is either fined or sent to prison , \" he added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"write\", does the participant \"anything\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I suspect the streets of Baghdad will look as if a war is looming this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suspect\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interfere\", does the participant \"State\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I apologize for the following inconvenience , but I have decided to move this group to Yahoo , so that we can post files and photos and other useful things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"apologize\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They love leaf or romaine lettuce and tomatos , celery , cucumbers , carrots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"lettuce\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launch\", does the participant \"circle\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yesterday evening , the Posada story was featured in the public television news show in Germany ( ARD , Tagesthemen ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"featured\", does the participant \"ARD\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defied\", does the participant \"Winter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Rumsfeld , Wolfowitz and Feith staffed the CPA with Neoconservatives , most of whom had no administrative experience , no Arabic , and no respect for Muslim culture ( or knowledge about it ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"staffed\", does the participant \"Rumsfeld\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( The heat increases their \" production \" of musk . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increases\", does the participant \"heat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" I hope that industry , if put to the test , can do better [ than the government ] , but I do not expect it , \" Griffin added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I highlight the relevant skills in the summary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"highlight\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We have and will have children of our own , grandchildren too .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Musk , which is scraped from their genitals once a day for as long as they can surv ive , makes the scent of perfume last a bit longer after each application .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"Musk\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"An analysis of 65 bird species in the United Kingdom shows about one - third are laying their eggs four to seven days earlier than they did 25 years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laying\", does the participant \"eggs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe national reconciliation to be the only path forward to a new Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have the best prices locally and good customer service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"prices\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Jana made me feel very comfortable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Jana\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had the morelias enchiladas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"SCALIA filed a dissenting opinion , in which THOMAS and ALITO joined .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"SCALIA\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Her husband became a citizen of the US just the week before last .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"became\", does the participant \"husband\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cover letters and resumes need to be perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"letters\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( '' We have three generations of martyrs : grandmothers , mothers , daughters . '' )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have no complaints about the service I received .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You take a boat across the river , then spend a day biking , eating at a local restaurant , buying souvenirs and doing other things that are geared towards tourists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"souvenirs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need to have a form filled out that says I do n't have health insurance coverage through Enron .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had my wedding luncheon at this BJ s restaurant , and it was one of the best choices that I made .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"luncheon\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Police in the Indian capital Delhi say they have arrested the suspected co-ordinator and financier of last month 's deadly bomb blasts in the city .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"co-ordinator\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The clerics demanded talks with local US commanders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"demanded\", does the participant \"talks\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We played a new version of Uno called \" African Uno \" that was complex , fast and at times , physically challenging .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"played\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is PG&E 's Gas Accord II ( GA II ) Settlement Proposal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Proposal\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My father re-secured the petroleum assets of Kuwait in 1991 at a cost of sixty - one billion U.S. dollars ( $ 61,000,000,000 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-secured\", does the participant \"father\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I survived it without a problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"survived\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Her husband became a citizen of the US just the week before last .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"became\", does the participant \"husband\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a parakeet named Cookie . :P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"parakeet\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The classes cover all age and skill ranges , with BALLROOM , LATIN , SEQUENCE , STREET , DISCO , LINE DANCING , BALLET , TAP & JAZZ .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cover\", does the participant \"ranges\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"That indicates that they thrive in different water chemistries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicates\", does the participant \"That\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work with him and since past 6 years he is hosting his websites to Liquidweb .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My car broke down and roadside towed my vehicle to Sussman Kia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broke\", does the participant \"car\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Wiki Media Foundation , the group behind the Wikipedia online encyclopedia project , said Friday that search giant Google has volunteered to host some of its content on company servers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Foundation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Inhibitory Systems Control the Pattern of Activity in the Cortex\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Control\", does the participant \"Systems\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Meats are kept VERY cold , seafood smells fresh and the serving bar is VERY clean .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"smells\", does the participant \"seafood\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think he did it on purpose because of my simple request for another slice of grandma that was n't so well - done ( actually , burnt ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We sued Houston Casualty last year but I do n't recall making any bad faith claims .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sued\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"'' We have a very small number of forces in Shindand with a few helicopters , '' says Barno .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Barno\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We respect the fact that debate and discussion continue in many of our religious communities as to the scriptural , theological and liturgical issues involved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continue\", does the participant \"debate\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Denial of the status of marriage to those who would freely accept its responsibilities creates legal and economic inequities and social injustice .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"creates\", does the participant \"inequities\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launch\", does the participant \"circle\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I hope the above is clear .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last month , Nasrallah announced that his party would close ranks with Hamas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"announced\", does the participant \"Nasrallah\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the participant \"agency\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"drafted\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We oppose the use of sacred texts and religious traditions to deny legal equity to same - gender couples .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deny\", does the participant \"equity\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( Newsweek reported that Bush commanded his cabinet , \" Let heads roll ! \" )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commanded\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Plans are to build a private pipeline to Equilon 's West Delta # 143 platform and then bring the oil onshore .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"build\", does the participant \"pipeline\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They gave the best service & rates I could find .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"According to some reports , Zawahiri is thought by intelligence to be somewhere near the border of Pakistan and Afghanistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"Zawahiri\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the photo on the couch , the pillow she is resting on clashes with everything else in the shot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"resting\", does the participant \"she\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I used to tan down the street before I was referred to this place by one of my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( i know that snakes that have problems going to the bathroom wo n't eat . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"snakes\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My wife know my harmless secret and supports me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"wife\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"U.S. President George W. Bush shakes hands with Chinese President Hu Jintao in a bilateral meeting in Santiago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shakes\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"NASA has some PR hurdles to overcome in the future .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"hurdles\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the participant \"%\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the participant \"Allawi\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They both went to jail and a new manager was put in charge of the apartments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Paul McCartney said that George Harrison is a nothing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"McCartney\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"James J. Hoecker , the former Federal Energy Regulatory Commission chairman , defended making the December decision and also defended Winter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defended\", does the participant \"Hoecker\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need to check out the French Indochina War ( 1946 - 1954 ) not the Vietnam War ( 1957 - 1975 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"check\", does the participant \"War\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Al - Iraqiyah tv said that ICDC were controlling Ramadi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"controlling\", does the participant \"ICDC\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Denial of the status of marriage to those who would freely accept its responsibilities creates legal and economic inequities and social injustice .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"creates\", does the participant \"Denial\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Fried rice has NO flavor , it literally taste like water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rice\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"She gave me amazing pictures at an amazing price and made my wedding day so memorable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"She\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"wolf\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"George Harrison said that he is tired of listening to people talk about John Lennon ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Harrison\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He and his master dragged me to my room and held judgment upon me as a convicted traitress .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dragged\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it was in the Lincoln Square area but do n't quote me on that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Americans detected the attempt to infiltrate the urban areas and were already redeploying troops from the rural areas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detected\", does the participant \"attempt\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I left with a case of BRAWLER !!!! !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"THEY HAVE EXCELLENT SUSHI CHEF SPECIAL ROLLS FOR A FAIR PRICE AND SO IS THE GRILL ORDERS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAVE\", does the participant \"THEY\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You need to check out the French Indochina War ( 1946 - 1954 ) not the Vietnam War ( 1957 - 1975 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"check\", does the participant \"War\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i emailed you saaaaaam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"emailed\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cover letters and resumes need to be perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"letters\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The plants provide shade and root strength for bank stability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"plants\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Wiki Media Foundation , the group behind the Wikipedia online encyclopedia project , said Friday that search giant Google has volunteered to host some of its content on company servers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Foundation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I needed a part for my appliance , the cost was very high so I said never mind , paid the fee and called a local business for a second quote .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"fee\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Google\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" The impacts of global warming are affecting people now in the Arctic , \" said ACIA chair Robert Corell .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Corell\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I loved the car so we began negotiating my trade - in and the price of the 09 XF .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loved\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"woken\", does the participant \"boyfriend\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Yahoo! Mail has the best spam protection around\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Mail\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"she knows she is invading someone else 's territory , but ca n't help it , and has no where to go .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invading\", does the participant \"she\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accumulate\", does the participant \"minimum\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The German Expressionist movement was destroyed as a result .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroyed\", does the participant \"movement\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have no inside information , but I have been following links today that strongly indicate that Google is damn serious about securing permanent control of the leading edge browser technology in Firefox .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"following\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the meantime , we extend our best wishes for a safe and happy holiday season .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Either I suck at my own style or Janice is a genius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suck\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He told us to stop by the salon and then he will tell us the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"us\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I ran into Corey last night at LW s and I am thinking this is a girl for Darren .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( I know , ignorant question ) Then why call them , or any other phonies ' Christians ' , even if they themselves claim the appellation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"From the delectable Antipasto Misto to the Spaghetti alla Barese and the Parmigiana and ending with gelato , all was mouth watering .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"watering\", does the participant \"all\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The investors put big bucks into the building but are clueless about what makes a good dining or bar experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the participant \"investors\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is a forecast for the rest of the summer for the X ( NWP and PGT ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"forecast\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"sorry , i left lou off of the message .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He earned 137 points in 1970 - 1971 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"earned\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bangs said his agency is still reviewing the decision .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Bangs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Abdel Rahman 's son was captured in Quetta , Pakistan in mid-February 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"captured\", does the participant \"son\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left with a case of BRAWLER !!!! !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"woken\", does the participant \"boyfriend\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cities such as Falluja received special treatment from Saddam and enjoyed a disproportionate share of the country 's wealth and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"treatment\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sussexs have soft feathers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"feathers\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" I 'm pretty suspicious of making broad generalizations , \" however , he cautioned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cautioned\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i want a small indoor pet that my mother will let me have please help\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"staff\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Terrell , a CIA asset originally recruited for the Contra effort , identifies the man attempting to recruit him into the Philippine scheme as Oliver North ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"identifies\", does the participant \"Terrell\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess I 'm extremely fortunate that I received a scholarship which paid about 800 f my course fees through my degree .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I work with him and since past 6 years he is hosting his websites to Liquidweb .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Our system reflects SJ Bondad GDP but SWG is going to pay us based on SJ Non-Bondad GDP .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"us\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"patience\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I assume you are talking about a pacman frog .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assume\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need a background in law enforcement .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"background\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe that there might be a sign - flipping problem for PUTS that 's causing this whole issue .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I purchased a 2 - year old certified pre-owned BMW from this dealership .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"BMW\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You take a boat across the river , then spend a day biking , eating at a local restaurant , buying souvenirs and doing other things that are geared towards tourists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"souvenirs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I saw a site that charges $ 0.70 per mile .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"site\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"China and Japan , and the world at large , have more dollar reserves than they require .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"China\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He earned 137 points in 1970 - 1971 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"earned\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"guys\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Olympus X - 940 14 Megapixel Digital Camera has filters and can do all sorts of special effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Camera\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the participant \"food\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I adopted a 3.5 month old yellow lab last winter from the Dumb Friends League .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adopted\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I want to go all over :) I do n't have a set route yet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It incorporates Mr. Stojic 's and Mr. Kelly 's initial comments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporates\", does the participant \"comments\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Reggie said he will pay us soon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Reggie\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In a highly significant move Afghan Pashtun tribes along the Pakistan border warned the Taliban in Quetta and Chaman that if they try and disrupt the elections , they would be resisted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"disrupt\", does the participant \"elections\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At 3:15 am on night # 2 , the fire alarm and strobe light activated in my room .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"activated\", does the participant \"alarm\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"acted\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I decided that Nicki would just have to wait on her own .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"decided\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There 's no tracking mechanism in place \" ?!?!?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"'s\", does the participant \"mechanism\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the participant \"agency\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"& I wan na know what food has the game pieces .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wan\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He told us to stop by the salon and then he will tell us the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One witness at the Moutasaddiq trial in Germany alleged that Zarqawi had not allowed Monotheism and Holy War to share resources with al - Qaeda in the early zeroes of the 21st century .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"allowed\", does the participant \"Zarqawi\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Biloxi , 30 people were reported dead in one block of flats which was hit by a 9 m ( 30 ft ) \" storm surge \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"people\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I spoke with Mike Collins [ 203-719-8385 ( phone ) and 203-719-7031 ( fax ) ] who conrfirmed to me that the cap included the remaining 2.5 + million remaining shares .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"rights\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrived\", does the participant \"kids\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another connection to Philippine terror and weapons smuggling - dating from the 1980s - is alleged in the book Disposable Patriot , by Jack Terrell .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"alleged\", does the participant \"connection\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i wish the other utilities i had to set up had people to work with like this ..\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I dropped the truck off in the morning and it was ready that afternoon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Their chauvinisms got to the point that even they themselves hated each other .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hated\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cripple\", does the participant \"destroyer\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchase\", does the participant \"meal\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Pound for pound , mountain lions eat more game and more livestock than wolves .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"game\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He said the top three cartoons will be announced on September 2 , with the winners being awarded prizes of 12,000 , 8,000 and 5,000 dollars respectively .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love it for discounted beauty items and household appliances .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They phoned the same day , confirmed it was the gearbox quoted me the job , I gave the go ahead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"phoned\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]